>> Brian Holt: 因此，我们想要合并详细信息，因此
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So
we wanna wrap details in this, so
如果 API 有错误，它不会崩溃。
in case there's an error from the API,
that it doesn't crash.
>> Brian Holt: 现在，我很想把这个错误的内部
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Now, I would be super
tempted to wrap this inside of an error
边界。
boundary.
但有一件事你必须了解错误的界限
But there's a big thing that you
have to know about error boundaries,
它只是在里面和里面的孩子一起工作
is it only works with
children inside of it.
这是一个 ErrorBoundary 。
This was an ErrorBoundary here.
>> Brian Holt: 或 ErrorBoundary?
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Or ErrorBoundary?
>> Brian Holt: 这不起作用。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: This wouldn't work.
原因是你要
And the reason being is that you would
在轮播中捕捉到一些东西但你不能把它们抓进去
catch things in carousel, but you wouldn't
catch them inside of the class itself.
所以它无法在它所进入的类别中捕捉它
So it can't catch it inside
of the class that it's in, so
我们必须把它做个更高级的部分
we have to make it basically a higher
order component above details.
我给你们展示一个真正的方法。
And I'll show you just a really
quick way of doing that.
所以不要把细节都搞乱了
So rather than mess with details itself,
我们要做的就是要在这里出口默认的功能
what we're gonna do is we're going
to export a default function here.
>> Brian Holt: 函数，将会被称为 " 详细信息 " 。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Function,
there it's going to be called Details.
>> Brian Holt: WthErrorBoundary。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: WthErrorBoundary.
> > Brian Holt: 它会被道具，还会回来
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: It's gonna take in props,
and it's going to return
ErrorBoundary， >> Brian Holt: And
an ErrorBoundary,
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And
然后就会在里面呈现细节
then, it's going to render
details inside of it.
>> Brian Holt: 因此，这会自动在此处导入 ErrorBoundary ，因此
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So this automatically
imported up here ErrorBoundary as well, so
确保你能像我一样把它进口到第四行
make sure you import that
there like I did on line four.
> > Brian Holt: 然后在这里，我们仍然有这个问题。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And then down here,
we still have a problem with this.
因此，这会在 " 详细信息" 周围正确包装 ErrorBoundary 。
So this is correctly wrapping
an ErrorBoundary around Details.
现在这将会捕捉到各种不同的
And now this will catch all
of the various different
在 " 详细信息 " 中可能发生的错误。
errors that could happen
inside of Details.
但我们有这些道具
But we have these props.
我们想把这些道具传递到细节上。
And we want to pass these
props into Details.
我们要怎么做
How do we do that?
我是说你可以做些像 props=props 的东西
I mean, you could do something
like props=props, but
这不太一样
this isn't quite the same.
>> Brian Holt: 因为现在在这里，我得说 props.props。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Because now inside of here,
I would have to say this.props.props.
会很奇怪那就不对了
It would be weird, so that's not right.
我可以把所有细节都找出来
I could go figure out everything
that Details is getting from
其父组件，然后按名称将其传入。
its parent components, and
then, by name, pass them in.
但这很麻烦我也不想这么做
But that's burdensome,
I don't want to do that either.
所以我要给你看一下你也能做的小把戏
So I'm gonna show you a little
trick that you can do as well.
你可以把这些花括号放在这里说  就像这样。
You can actually just put these curly
braces here and say  like that.
这将在 " 详细信息 " 中传播道具。
This is going to spread
the props across Details.
所以想象一个道具有一些
So imagine for
a second that props had some,
什么是 " 详细信息 " 从道具中使用 ?
what is Details even using from props?
普罗普斯
Props.
>> Brian Holt: 标识，对吗 ?
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: ID, right?
所以它得到了 ID
So it's getting ID.
>> Brian Holt: 因此，这等于表示 id=，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So this would be
equivalent from saying id=,
然后把所有这些都写出来
and then writing out all
of those piece by piece.
这只是一种更快的方法。
This is just a faster way of doing it.
>> 布莱恩 - 霍尔特: 现在，让我给你一个提醒你的故事。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Now,
let me offer you a cautionary tale.
React的优点，我们使用 React 的原因是它非常明确。
The advantage of React, the reason why we
use React is because it's very explicit.
挺容易穿过去的
It's very easy to go through and
都能理解每一件事的一切
understand piece by piece
what everything is doing.
这里的 ErrorBoundary 没有互动，根本不关心道具，
ErrorBoundary here has no interaction and
does not care at all about the props,
它只是想包装点东西然后让它继续呈现
it's just trying to wrap something,
and then, let it continue rendering.
因此 ErrorBoundary 除了捕捉错误之外没有为你做任何事
So ErrorBoundary's not doing anything for
you other than catching errors, and
在这里做所有工作的细节
it's Details that's actually
doing all the work here.
所以我们想成为这个 DetailsWithErrorBoundary 的通行证。
So we just want to be a pass through for
this DetailsWithErrorBoundary.
我拼错了它是 DetailsWithErrorBoundary
I spelled that wrong,
it's DetailsWithErrorBoundary,
不是那事，只是为了调试目的，就这样。
not that that matters, that's just for
debugging purposes, and that's all.
>> Brian Holt: 因此，您只想在以下时间使用这些传播运算符 :
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So you only wanna
use these spread operators when
组件其实并不真正在乎那些道具是什么
the component doesn't actually really
care about what those props are.
这只是要经过一段
It's just meant to be a pass through.
不要用这种威利的方式，让你的代码更难解读。
Don't use this willy nilly, it makes your
code harder to read for the most part.
有道理吗
Make sense?
好的。
Okay.
> > Brian Holt: 那么现在，如果我们看看我们的应用程序，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So now,
if we go look at our app,
所有东西都应该是一模一样的
everything should look exactly
the same cuz this has no errors on it,
但如果我现在进入 " 详细信息 " 页面并表示 " 详细信息 " ，会发生什么情况 ?
but what happens if I go into
the Details page now and say Details?
>> Brian Holt: 在这里说，而不是 componentDidMount，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And let's say here
instead of componentDidMount,
我们只会说会有新的错误
we're just gonna say,
throw new Error like that.
> > Brian Holt: 会发生什么 ?
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: What's gonna happen?
希望您可以说此页面存在错误。
Hopefully, you can say that there
was an error with this page.
单击此处以返回，并等待 5 秒。
Click here to go back,
and wait five seconds.
我们要做 5 秒的工作我们还没完成那部分
We'll go do the five seconds part,
we haven't done that part.
您还可以在此处看到发生错误的情况。
You can also see here
that you get the error.
>> Brian Holt: 您可以看到 ErrorBoundary 捕获到错误。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And
you can see ErrorBoundary caught in error.
所以你做了这个信息，就是我发明的这个非常描述性的错误，
So you do the message, which is this very
descriptive error that I just invented,
它还提供了来自 componentDidMount的所有内容。
and it also gives you all of the stuff
where this came from componentDidMount.
Blah ， blah， blah，所有这些东西 .
Blah, blah, blah, all that kind of stuff.
>> Brian Holt: 现在，如果我们点击这里，它就会带我们回到这里。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Now, if we click here,
it'll take us back here.
现在，如果我们没有 ErrorBoundary ，这将会使整个程序崩溃。
Now, if we didn't have the ErrorBoundary,
this would just crash the entire program.
>> Brian Holt: 这就是 ErrorBoundaries 有用的东西。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So that's what
ErrorBoundaries are useful for.